





Carl[i] navarro (they/them)















ABOUT ME

I'm an experimental visual artist based in London. I have 3 years experience producing graphics, operations of A/V equipment for live game shows and installation of bespoke still/video capture systems.

I'm an inventive and logically driven individual with a desire to further improve problem solving and technical skills.

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Fluently bilingual in English and Spanish, and actively studying beginner Swedish.
- Adept in using computer systems and a variety of multimedia software.
- Able to communicate clearly with both team members and clients.
- Knowledgeable in audio-visual equipment, including maintenance and troubleshooting.
- Experience in building computers and programming Arduinos and Pis.
- Ability to quickly adapt and actively learn in fast-paced, evolving environments.

CONTACT DETAILS

Github: github.com/c4rli

Email: carlos@viscoplastique.xyz Website: viscoplastique.xyz

EDUCATION

Trilogy Education

Front End Development Bootcamp | 2022 - present

King's College London

BSc CompSci w/ Management (CertHE) | 2019 - 2021

Newham College

Computer Systems Eng. (Distinction) | 2018 - 2019

St. Aloysius College

10 GCSE (A*-A) | 2008 - 2013

TECHNICAL CONFIDENCE

OBS Adobe Photoshop Adobe Premiere Pro

JavaScript **UNIX Shell** CSS Python

HTMI

Photography Videography

Windows Systems macOS Systems

Linux (Ubuntu)

WORK HISTORY

THE FLASH PACK

Junior Creative Technologist | March 2022 - present

- Specified and planned technical solutions to meet project requirements and briefs.
- Tested, maintained and catalogued NUCs, cameras, printers and servers in a technical workshop.
- Created user manuals for systems and trained non-technical staff on setup and operation.
- Responded to technical support issues raised via remote support ticketing dashboard.
- Conducted onsite installation of technical setups in the UK and abroad.
- Performed research and development of new ideas from a brief and created detailed reports.

AGENCY UNKNOWN

Vision Mixer & A/V Technician | Oct. 2020 - present

- Executed interactive, live game shows for up to 200 participants via video conferencing software.
- Maintained A/V equipment, including cameras, lighting, monitors and microphones, in a professional studio environment.
- Provided training and support to non-technical staff and guest hosts on the effective use of studio equipment.
- Developed and integrated dynamic, custom assets for OBS, streamlining the process through the creation of robust Streamdeck command profiles.
- Collaborated closely with clients ensuring technical aspects of shows align with preferences, including custom backgrounds, logos, and color themes.

